제작 - 네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
`
제작 - 네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
위스콘신주 포인트플레이스
Point Place, Wisconsin
1976년 11월 24일
november 24th, 1976
오후 3시 45분
3:45 p.m.
버스 정류장
The Bus Station
누나 버스는 아직 안 왔어요
Laurie's bus isn't here yet.
아빠, 차에 들어가서 히터켜고
있어도 돼요? 얼어 죽겠어요
Dad, can we get in the car
and turn on the heat? I'm freezing.
너 편하게 해주려고
기름 낭비할 생각 없다
I'm not wasting gas
just so you can be comfortable.
그럼 안에 들어가서 기다려요
Can we at least go wait inside?
난 저 사람들이랑 대합실 안에
같이 안 있을거야
I'm not going in that bus station
with those people.
저 얼어 죽겠어요
God, I'm freezing.
참, 에릭, 깜빡했는데
로리가 친구를 데려온다는 구나
Oh, Eric, I forgot to tell you.
Your sister's bringing a friend home...
그러니까 넌
지하실에서 자야 될거야
so you'll be sleeping
in the basement.
지하실요?
누나방에서 재우면 되잖아요
The basement?
They should sleep in Laurie's room.
여보, 생각해 봤는데요
And Red, I've been thinking.
이번 추수감사절엔 커다란 칠면조는
생략해야 할까 봐요
Maybe this Thanksgiving
we should skip the big turkey.
피글리 위글리에서
작은 칠면조를 세일하더라구요
Small ones are on sale
at Piggly-Wiggly.
우리 가족은
명절에 구두쇠 짓 안해
This family doesn't
scrimp on holidays.
어머니가 닭 앞에
앉아 있는 걸 상상해 봐
Can you imagine my mother
sitting down to a chicken?
여보, 당신 어머니는 어차피 내가 만든
음식 안 먹으니까 상관 없어요
Red, your mother
won't eat my cooking anyway...
so that won't be a problem.
아빠, 걔네들이
지하실에서 자야 돼요
Dad, they should sleep
in the basement.
작년 추수감사절에 어머니가 턱이
약해서 칠면조 못 씹겠다고 하셨잖아요
Red, last Thanksgiving she said
her jaw wasn't strong enough...
to chew the turkey.
그건 정말 훌륭한
칠면조였단 말이에요
And that was a magnificent turkey.
아빠, 제 방이에요
Dad, it's my room.
- 그거 만드려고 얼마나 애를 썼는데
- 거기까지! 그만해
- I work myself to the bone for that...
- all right, that's it! Hold it.
여보, 어머니 일로 흥분하지 마
Now, Kitty, don't get worked up
over my mother.
그리고 넌 지하실에서 자!
And you, you're sleeping
in the basement!
그리고 우린 빌어먹게 행복한
추수감사절을 보낼거야
And we're all having
a happy damn Thanksgiving!
엄마, 아빠
얘는 케이트에요
Mommy, Daddy. This is Kate.
안녕하세요?
Hi.
어서 와라, 얘야
차에 타자, 너 얼어 죽겠다
Hi, sweetheart. Let's get in the car,
you must be freezing.
네가 에릭이구나
So, you're Eric.
너희 누나가 네가 이렇게
귀엽다는 말은 안 하던데
Your sister didn't tell me
you were so cute.
이번 주말이 재밌어 지겠는걸
We are going to have
so much fun this weekend.
제 방에서 주무시면 돼요
You can sleep in my room.
- 네 방에다 짐 갖다놔라
- 네
- Get Kate settled into your room.
- Yeah.
맞다. 야, 니 G.I. 조 인형들도
쟤한테 잊지말고 보여줘
Oh, yeah, and hey, don't forget to
show her your GI Joe dolls.
그거 좋은 생각인데
That's such a good idea.
아빠한테 니가 데이트하는 교수에
대해 털어놓을 기회가 생길 거 아냐
That'll give you a chance to tell Dad
about that professor you're dating.
- 뭐?
- 아빠, 농담이에요
- What?
- Dad, he's joking.
오늘밤에 너무 춥지 않았으면 좋겠다
난 실은 다 벗고 자거든
Gosh, I hope it doesn't get too cold
tonight. I sleep practically naked.
키티, 추수감사절 기대되죠?
So, Kitty, looking forward
to Thanksgiving?
그래요
Yes.
시어머니가 오실 거예요
Red's mother is coming.
그 양반이 당신한테 붙여준
애칭은 뭐예요?
What's that pet name
she has for you?
'창녀'요
Whore.
그래도 그 양반이 그이를 괴롭히는
거에 비하면 아무것도 아니에요
Oh, you know, she doesn't bother
me as much as she does Red,
그이는 크리스마스도 다가오는데
파트타임 일밖에 못해서
and he's tense enough,
what with Christmas coming up...
- 벌써 꽤 스트레스를 받고 있어요
- 파트타임요? 정말 힘들겠네요
and him only working part-time.
Part-time, that's rough.
우리 그이가 스트레스 받을때
우린 같이 거품목욕을 해요
Oh, When Bob gets tense,
we take a bubble bath together.
그이는 내 알몸을 적셔주면
긴장이 풀리나 봐요
Soaking my naked body
really relaxes him.
기분 좋아
Oh, yeah.
- 엄마, 할머니 전화요
- 가봐야 겠어요
- Mom, Grandma's on the phone!
- I gotta go.
토퍼 그레이스 (에릭 포먼)
밀라 커니스 (재키 벅하트)
애쉬튼 커쳐 (마이클 켈소)
대니 메스털슨 (스티븐 하이드)
로라 프레폰 (도나 핀씨오티)
윌머 발더라마 (페즈)
데브라 조 러프 (키티 포먼)
커트우드 스미스 (레드 포먼)
타냐 로버츠 (미지 핀씨오티)
돈 스탁 (밥 핀씨오티)
That '70s Show 자막팀
영문자막 : 김민경(paramount@nate)
싱크수정, 번역 : 김현정(fuchs@nate)
That '70s Show 자막팀
영문자막 : 김민경(paramount@nate)
싱크수정 : 김현정(fuchs@nate)
1x09 Thanksgiving
Nov 22, 1998 on FOX
케이트 말야, 섹시해?
So this Kate, is she hot?
당연 섹시하지
여대생은 다 섹시해
Of course she's hot.
All college girls are hot.
대학소개 책자 다 봤잖아
I mean, we've all seen
the brochures, right?
도나, 음악 트는 거 좀 도와줘
지금 당장
Okay, Donna. Help me play
some music. Right now.
- 섹시하단 말이지?
- 장난 아냐
- So she's hot.
- Oh, so hot.
좋아
Okay.
너 괜찮아?
Are you okay?
- 음.. 응
- 도나, 어떻게 괜찮을 수 있니?
- Umm, yeah.
- Donna, how can you be okay?
여대생이 에릭 침대에서 자는데
There's a college woman
sleeping in his bed.
에릭은 지하실에서 잘 거야
He's sleeping in the basement.
도나, 발정난 고등학생 개한테
계단쯤은 문제가 안돼
Donna, stairs are not gonna
stop a high school horndog.
발정난 고등학생 개는
가시 철조망으로도 못 막아
Barbed wire will not stop
a high school horndog.
- 불의 장벽도 발정난...
- 재키, 알았어, 알았다고
- A wall of fire will not stop a high...
- Jackie, I get it, I get it.
불쌍한 도나
Poor Donna.
너무 순진하구나
So naive.
그래서 인제 뭐 할거야?
So what do you guys wanna do?
에릭
Eric,,,
오늘밤에 너무 춥지 않았으면 좋겠다
I hope it doesn't get
too cold tonight,
난 사실 다 벗고 자거든
I sleep practically naked,
다 벗고
Naked,
맞다..
Yeah...
나 가봐야 될 거 같아
well, I guess I'm just gonna...
그러니까.. 너무 피곤해서..
Just gonna... I'm tuckered out...
그래서.. 집에 간다!
so... I might as well go home.
학교 얘기를 좀 해보렴
So, tell me about school.
저 철학을 전공하기로 했어요
Oh, well, I've decided to
major in philosophy.
좋은 생각이야, 그린 베이에
큰 철학 공장이 문을 열었잖아
That's good, because they just opened up
that big philosophy factory in Green Bay.
에릭, 웃긴다는 거에 대해 내가 너한테
뭐라고 그랬지? / 전 안 웃긴다고요
Eric, what did I tell you
about being funny? / I'm, I'm not.
맞다. 가서 차고나 쓸어라
That's right. Now, sweep the garage.
네
Yes, sir.
최초 이민자들이 셀러리에 땅콩버터를
바르는 이 비법을 알기나 했을까 몰라
I wonder if the Pilgrims
were clever enough...
to put peanut butter on their celery.
여보, 전화 좀 받아
나 서랍 고치고 있잖아
Kitty, could you get that?
I'm fixing the drawer.
너무 하네요
Oh, dear God.
당신 어머니가 벌써 오늘 아침에만
5번 전화하셨다구요
Your mother has already called me
five times this morning.
- 당신이 받아요
- 여보, 난 통화하기 싫어
- You answer it.
- Kitty, I don't want to talk to her.
당신을 낳아주셨잖아요
She gave birth to you.
여보세요
Hello.
네, 엄마
Hi, Ma.
정말요?
Really?
당신 바꿔달래
It's for you.
네, 어머니
Hello, Mother Forman.
아까 말씀드렸잖아요
인제 30분이나 됐나..
Uhuh, just like I told you,
I don't know, half an hour ago...
애들이 내일 정오에
모시러 갈 거예요
the kids will be there at noon
to pick you up.
네, 맞아요. 전 버릇이 없죠
그럼 끊어요
Yep, you're right. I need to
work on my attitude. Bye then.
있잖니..
You know...
빌 바우어랑 결혼할 걸 그랬나봐
I could have married Bill Bower.
그 사람 어머니는 죽었거든
His mother was dead.
그 친구가 나한테 화내면 어떡해?
What if he yells at me?
화 안낼 거예요
당신이 호의를 베푸는 거잖아요
He's not gonna yell at you.
You're doing him a favor.
어서 가봐요!
Go. Go!
레드, 여기서 자넬 만나다니 놀랍구만
Red, what a surprise to run into you.
난 여기 산다네, 밥
I live here, Bob.
그렇지
Yep.
그럼 난 들어가네
Okay, I'm going in.
사실은, 레드
부탁하고 싶은게 있는데
Actually, Red,
I just wanted to ask you a favor.
내 전자제품 가게가
연휴 내내 아주 바쁘거든
My appliance store
gets real busy all over the holidays...
그래서 일손이 좀 필요하다네
and I could use a little
help down there.
나한테 일자리를 제의하는 건가?
You offering me a job?
오해하지 않았으면 좋겠어
이건 자선이 아니라네
Now I don't want you to get
the wrong idea. This is not charity.
- 자선?
- 아니, 자선이 아니라고
- Charity?
- No, not charity.
어쨌거나 난 일거리 필요없네
I'm not looking for work anyway, Bob.
- 그래도...
- 잘 자게, 밥!
- But...
- Goodnight, Bob!
거봐, 여보
화낼 거라고 했잖아!
Midge, he yelled at me!
들어오세요
Come in.
우와
Wow.
뭐?
What?
음.. 잘 때 입을 거 좀
가지러 왔어요
Um, I was just coming up here
to get something to sleep in.
그러니까...
So...
그럼 나중에 봐야 겠네요
I guess I'll see you later then.
원한다면 잠깐 얘기나 하자
You can stay and talk a minute,
if you want.
좋아요
Okay.
문 닫아
Close the door.
네
Okay.
그래서...
So...
케이트
Kate...
캐서린을 줄여서 부르는 거죠?
that's short for Katherine, right?
그래
Yeah.
앉아
Have a seat.
그래, 가고 싶은 학교는 생각해 봤니?
So, have you thought about
where you want to go to school yet?
글쎄요, 전 누나네 학교가 좋아요
Oh, well, I like your school.
정말이지...
I found that it was really...
난 이제 자야겠다
I have to go to bed now.
우린 벌써 침대 위에 있잖아요
Wait, we are in bed.
아, 맞다, 알았어요
Oh, okay, I see.
좋아요
Okay.
그럼, 잘 자
So, good night.
잘 자요
Good night.
에릭
Eric.
잠깐만요
Just... one second?
야구, 베트남, 리처드 닉슨
Okay, baseball, Vietnam,
Richard Nixon,,,
팻 닉슨, 팻 분, 일기예보하는 여자
아냐, 이건 아냐!
Pat Nixon, Pat Boone,
the girl that does the weather...no, No!
좋아, 해파리, 정말 큰 거미
Okay, jelly fish, really big spiders,
빨리, 더 쎈 걸로, 좋아
Come on, dig deep, okay,
마당에서 후진하다가 스키퍼를 친 날
The day we backed over Skipper
in the driveway,,,
농업박람회 가는 대신 그 녀석을
뒷마당에 묻어야 했지
and instead of going to the county fair,
I had to bury him in the backyard,
됐어요
Okay.
난 괜찮아요
I'm good.
잘 자요
And good night.
좋은 아침, 여보
행복한 추수감사절 되세요
Good morning, Red.
Happy Thanksgiving.
그래
Yeah.
당신 정말 일찍 일어났군
You're up awful early.
당신 어머니가 새벽 5시에 전화했을 때
운좋게 전화벨 소리를 들었거든요
Well, luckily I heard the phone ring...
when your mother called
at 5:00 this morning.
그래, 그거... 운 좋구만
Yeah, that.. that is lucky.
오, 잊어버릴까봐 미리 말하는데
Oh, before I forget...
로리가 크리스마스 선물로
원하는 게 있대 요
Laurie told me
what she wants for Christmas.
기숙사 방에 놓을
휴대용 TV요
A portable TV for her dorm room.
난 파트타임 일을 하는데
딸은 TV가 갖고 싶다니, 잘 됐군
I'm working part-time,
she wants a TV. Great.
밥이 하나 싸게 줄지도 모르죠
Maybe Bob can get you
a good deal on one from his store.
그 망할 밥한테서는
어떤 도움도 필요없어
I don't need any help
from that damn Bob.
어제 나한테 뭐라고 했는지 알아?
You know what he did yesterday?
- 일자리를 제안하더군
- 그래요?
- He offered me a job.
- He did?
그런 악마같은 인간 피해서
이사가야 겠어요
Oh, we have to move away
from such an evil man.
당신 오늘 아침에 너무 재밌군
Hell, you're a lot of fun
in the morning.
이봐요, 칠면조 소년
Hey, turkey boy.
내장 좀 보여줄래요?
Wanna show me your giblets?
그래서 여대생이랑 키스했단 말야?
So you made out with a college girl?
그런 셈이지
Kind of.
말해봐
Start talking.
소설처럼 말해줘
야한 소설처럼
Tell it like a story, like a sexy story.
좋아
Okay.
내 입안에 혀를
통째로 집어 넣더라고
She, like, jammed her
entire tongue into my mouth.
너희들 여자애 혀가
그렇게 큰 줄 모를걸, 안 그래?
And you wouldn't think a girl had,
like, that much tongue, you know?
대단한데!
That's great.
오, 그럼
Oh, oh yeah.
왜?
What?
모르겠어, 죄책감이 들어
I don't know, I feel kind of guilty.
너무 추잡한 것 같아
Almost like dirty.
추잡한 건 좋은거야
Dirty is good.
나도 추잡한 느낌 좋아
I like feeling dirty.
아니, 아냐, 나 기분이 안 좋아
No, no, I mean, I feel bad.
나 도나에게 말해야 될 거 같아
Look, I think I gotta tell Donna.
정말?
Really?
그럼, 이 세상 남자들을 대신해서...
Well, on behalf of men everywhere.
맞아, 그러니까 들키기 전까지는
양다리 걸치고 있는 거야
Yeah, man, I mean
the right thing to do...
is juggle them both
until it all blows up in your face.
너희들은 이해못해
난 아무 것도 숨길 수 없어
Look, you guys don't understand.
I can't hide anything.
도나는 날 보자마자 알아챌 거야
The minute she looks at me
she's gonna know.
무슨 얘기들 하고 있니?
What are you guys talking about?
나 어떤 여자랑 키스했어
I kissed a girl.
- 망했다!
- 이 멍청한 놈!
- Shocking!
- I am appalled!
뭐 어째?
You what?
로리가 데려온 여자애 알지?
You know that friend
my sister brought home from college?
- 그 걸레?
- 맞아
- The slutty one.
- Yeah.
걔한테 키스했어
Um, I kissed her.
- 나한테 그 얘길 왜 하는 거야?
- 죄책감이 들어서
- Why are you telling me this?
- I, I feel guilty...
그게 정말
because it was like...
진짜 키스 같았거든
really kissing.
그럼 우리가 한 건
진짜 키스가 아니란 거야?
So what we do isn't really kissing?
우리가 뭔가 있는 사이란 걸 생각하면
너한테 말해야 한다고 생각했어
I thought you should know,
considering that you and I have a thing.
그렇지?
Right?
글쎄, 네가 걸레같은 계집애한테
Well, obviously we don't have a thing...
키스하고 돌아다니면 우리 사이는
아무 것도 아닌 거지, 그렇지?
if you're running around
kissing slutty girls, right?
너 화났구나
Okay, you're mad.
화났다고? 천만에
Mad? No.
화가 왜 나?
Why should I be mad?
사실 네가 원하면
무엇에라도 키스할 수 있겠지
I mean, in fact,
you can kiss whatever you want.
네 엉덩이에다 먼저 해!
Start with your own butt!
너희들 왜 여기 있는거냐?
왜 맨날 여기 있는 거야?
Why are you here?
Why are you always here?
추수감사절이잖아
너희들은 가족도 없냐?
It's Thanksgiving.
Don't you have families?
도나, 얘기 좀 할래?
Donna, you wanna talk?
- 도나가 잘 받아들이지 못한 거 같아
- 뭘 받아들이는데?
- I guess Donna didn't take it very well.
- Take what well?
에릭이 케이트랑 키스한 거요
Eric made out with Kate.
- 키스만?
- 아저씨 아들은 창녀에요
- Anything else?
- Your son is a whore.
에릭
Eric...
도나가 굉장히 화가 나서 가더구나
Donna just came through here
looking very upset.
왜 그러는지 아느냐?
Would you have any idea
what that's about?
몰라요. 같이 있을 땐 괜찮아 보였..
I have no idea.
She seemed fine when we...
- 벌써 아시는군요, 그렇죠?
- 당연히 알지
- You already know, don't you?
- Of course I know.
도나는 아주 다정한 아이다
Donna is such a sweet kid.
어떻게 걔한테 그럴 수가 있냐?
How could you do this to her?
모르겠어요
I don't know.
저한텐 맨날 나쁜 일만 생겨요
무슨 액운이라도 붙은 것 처럼요
You know, it seems like bad things
are always happening to me...
like I have bad luck or something.
아들아, 액운이 붙은 게 아냐
Son, you don't have bad luck.
너한테 안 좋은 일이 생기는 이유는
네가 멍청해서야
The reason that bad things
happen to you is
because you're a dumbass.
당장 가서 해결해
Now fix it.
도나..
Look, Donna...
음.. 얘기 좀 할래?
um, can we talk?
- 내가 자리를 비켜..
- 아뇨
- I'll leave you two...
- No.
여기 계세요
우리집엔 비밀같은 거 없어요
You should stay.
We don't have secrets in our house.
우린 딴 여자들한테 키스나 하는
발정난 쥐새끼처럼 서로를 속이지 않아요
We don't sneak around on each other
like a little horny rat kissing other girls.
도나..
Look, Donna...
추수감사절 디저트 먹으러
우리집에 와 줘
please come to my house
for Thanksgiving dessert.
다들 올 거야
너도 항상 왔잖아
Everyone's gonna be there.
You always come.
내 바보같은 행동때문에
그걸 망치면 안되잖아
Please don't let some stupid thing
that I did wreck that.
난 널 믿을 수 없어
Well, I can't depend on you...
근데 너는 왜 나한테
기대려고 하는 거야?
so why should you be able
to depend on me?
있지..
Look...
도나, 제발, 응?
Donna, please, okay?
정말 미안해
I'm really sorry.
- 나도 정말 괴로워
- 잘됐네!
- And I feel really bad.
- Good!
- 불쌍한 것
- 엄마!
- Poor thing.
- Mom!
너 말야
당연히 네가 불쌍하지
Oh, you. Of course I meant you.
요리 전문가로서
전 직접 확인하고 싶었습니다
As a food editor,
I wanted to find out for myself,,,
요즘 칠면조가
그렇게 좋은 이유를 말이죠
just what makes
the modern turkey so good,
아멘. 먹자!
Amen. Let's eat.
전부 다 차린건가 몰라?
아직도 뭘 빼먹은 거 같은데
Now, is everything on the table?
I still feel like I forgot something.
맙소사, 당신 어머니를 잊었어요
Oh, my God, I forgot your mother.
안돼!
No!
네, 어머니
Hello, Mother Forman.
아뇨, 잊긴요
No, I didn't forget you.
글쎄요? 애들이 30분 전에
모시러 갔거든요
I don't know, the kids left
a half hour ago to pick you up.
어떻게 된 건지 잘 모르겠네요
I can't imagine what's keeping them.
그거 내려놔요!
Put that back.
네
Hi,
아빠 차가 제 차를 막고 있어요
차키 주세요
The Toyota is blocking the car,
I need the keys.
아주 쬐끔만 기다려 주시겠어요?
제발 부탁인데, 빨리 가!
Could you hold on one teeny tiny
second? For the love of God, move!
정말 애들이 도착 안한 거 맞아요?
창 밖을 한번 내다 보세요
Are you sure they're not there?
Look out your window.
안경은 쓰고 계신 거죠?
Now do you have your glasses on?
할머니는 어디 계시냐?
Where's your grandma?
안 오신대요
She's not coming.
추수감사절 쇠러 사촌 조네로
갈 거라고 하셨어요
She said she's going
to Cousin Joel's for Thanksgiving.
아, 그것도 나쁘지 않구나
Ah, that's not so bad.
사실은 당신한테 마지막이
될 지도 모르는 추수감사절을
Actually, she said
it was a shame she couldn't spend...
가족과 지내지 못하는 게
수치스럽다고 하셨어요
what might be her
last Thanksgiving with her family.
그렇지만 우리끼리 즐겁게 지내길
바란다고 하셨어요
But she does hope
we all enjoy ourselves.
있잖니? 아주 잘됐구나
Well, you know what?
That's just fine.
내가 명절에 노인네 엉-덩-이
떠받들고 있을 필요 없으니 말이다
I don't need to kiss some old lady's
A-S-S on my holiday.
뭔소린지 알아버렸구나
You heard what I spelled.
신경 쓰지마
Forget it.
그러니까
So...
자네 가게에서는
직원 할인도 해 주나?
you give an employees' discount
down there at your store?
20%
Twenty percent.
그게 뭐든지 적용이 되나?
그러니까..
Does that cover,
anything like, say...
휴대용 TV 같은 것도?
portable TVs?
아, 그럼
Oh, heck, yeah.
축하하네, 밥
자네 방금 날 고용한 걸세
Congratulations, Bob,
you just hired me.
좋았어
잘 생각했네, 레드
Good. I'm glad to hear it, Red.
자네도 알지? 직장에서는 날
'핀씨오티 사장님'이라고 불러야 돼
You know, you'll have to
call me Mr. Pinciotti at work.
자네 그 표정
정말 맘에 든다니까
Oh, I got you good that time.
도나, 와줘서 정말 기뻐
Hey, Donna, I am so glad you came.
엄마가 시켜서 온 것 뿐이야, 알았어?
I only came
because my mom made me, okay?
도나, 좋았어, 어서 와
파이 좀 먹어라
Donna, all right, good to see you.
I got you some pie.
파이같은 거 먹기 싫어
I don't want any stupid pie.
뭐야? 내가 키스했냐?
What? I didn't kiss her.
안녕하세요, 아저씨
파이 좀 드실래요?
Hey, there, Bob.
You wanna piece of pie?
그래
Oh Yeah.
야, 도나
Hey, Donna.
- 야, 피곤하게 좀 굴지마!
- 아, 그러셔?
- Hey, don't get all tough with me!
- Oh, Yeah?
- 그래!
- 알았어
- Yeah!
- Okay, sure.
아냐, 우리 얘기 좀 해
- No. Look, we need to talk.
- I'll start. Get out!
나 먼저 할게
나가!
내가 무슨 말을 하길 바래?
벌써 사과 했잖아
What do you want me to say?
I already apologized.
내가 딴 여자랑 키스 좀 했다고
나랑 끝내고 싶은 거야?
You just want to forget about us
because I kissed some girl?
왜 그랬어?
Why'd you do it?
내가 멍청한 걸 말해야 아냐?
Well, I have it on pretty good authority
that I'm a dumbass.
그래서 좋았어?
So you liked it?
그래, 좋더라
Yeah, I liked it.
"아니"가 더 적절한 대답이었어
"No" would have been
a better answer.
도나
Donna...
있잖아
Iook...
그 키스는 정말 대단했어
that kiss was great...
그래도 되돌릴 수 있다면
난 그러겠어
and if I could take it back, I would.
왜냐면 그게 우리 사이를 망칠 만큼
대단할 수는 없으니까
Because it's not worth ruining
what you and I have.
에릭, 너 정말 멍청해
Eric, you are a dumbass.
그게 그러니까...
So is that like...
"널 용서할게, 이 멍청아" 인거야?
"I forgive you, dumb ass..."
아니면
"당장 나가, 이 멍청아"인거야?
or "Get out of my house,
you dumb ass"?
첫번째 거에 가까워
Mostly the first one.
우와
Wow.
- 혀잖아
- 그렇지
- Tongue.
- Oh, yeah.
좋아, 그럼 디저트 먹으러 가자
Okay well, let's go to dessert.
잠깐만 기다려 줄래?
Just, um, one second?
도나?
Donna?
잠깐이면 돼
Just one minute.
비단
Silk sheets,
조 네이머스의 엉덩이
뉴욕 제츠 팀의 미남 쿼터백
Joe Namath's butt,
딸기
Strawberries,
느린 춤
Slow dancing,
오, 균형이 안 맞아서 흔들리는 세탁기
Uh, the washing machine
with an unbalanced load,
됐어, 나 괜찮아
Well, I'm good.
너 어제밤 일 아무한테도
얘기 안했겠지, 했니?
You haven't told anybody else
about last night, have you?
곤란해 질까봐
I mean, it's kind of embarrassing.
내가 말야, 너 말고
I mean for me. Not you.
아니에요, 우리만의 비밀인 걸요
No, Kate, that's our little secret.
케이트, 너하고 에릭하고 응?
So, Kate, you and Eric?
영화 "졸업"에서 처럼
연상의 여인과 연하의 남자가 말야
Like The Graduate,
older woman, younger man.
있잖아, 커플 찢어놓기가
네 특기라면 말야
You know, if breaking up
couples is your thing...
나한테도 해주지 않을래?
왜냐면...
you can do your thing
with me 'cause...
마이클!
Michael!
안녕, 케이트
Hello, Kate.
그 거대한 혀 한번만 보여줄래?
May I see your giant tongue?
번역수정: 김찬미 (husseyttl@nate)
최종수정: 김현정(fuchs@nate)
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24